勒纳·钱 6-3 2-6 10-7 科博利 · 赛后场上采访
Learner Tien, and you've tied this thing up
勒纳·钱 你把比分扳平了
with an incredible match point.
靠一个不可思议的赛点
I want to know in this unique format,
我想问 在这种特别的赛制下
normally if you had lost a second set 6-2,
通常第二盘2比6输掉的话
you wouldn't have much momentum going
你不会有多少势头
into a third set.
带进第三盘
In this case, it's just a tiebreaker.
可这里只是一个抢十
After losing that second set,
丢掉第二盘之后
do you feel like things just reset
你会不会觉得一切都归零了
because it's just a tiebreaker to 10?
因为只是一个抢十？
Yeah, I mean, I think
是啊 我觉得
in general I can reset pretty well mentally.
总的来说我心态调整得挺快
I think that's a big strength of mine,
我觉得这是我的一大长处
but I think just in this format,
但我觉得在这种赛制里
you know, no matter what the score
不管比分是多少
is, I think everyone still has a chance.
我觉得每个人都还有机会
You know, the match can just turn
比赛可能一下子
on a dime.
就翻过来
So I think just being able to put
所以我觉得能把第二盘
the second behind me was really big today.
抛在脑后 今天真的很关键
Tactically speaking,
从战术上说
did you change anything
你有没有做什么调整
in that third set tiebreaker?
在决胜的抢十里？
I know this court is slow.
我知道这块场地很慢
Did you just tell yourself, I'm gonna go
你是不是跟自己说 我要
into lockdown mode and not miss?
进入锁死模式 不再失误？
Yeah, that's what my teammates told me
对 这正是队友们跟我说的话
in between the second and third just to go
在第二盘和第三盘之间 让我
into lockdown.
进入锁死模式
And I was able to do it
大部分时间
for most of the breaker,
我都做到了
but there are some moments
但有些时候
where the ball just seems very enticing
球看起来特别诱人
to go for it.
忍不住想去打
But Taylor actually told me
不过弗里茨跟我说
that the 8-7 point was the first point
8比7那一分是第一分
in the whole breaker that whoever
整个抢十里 谁在进攻
was on offense actually won the point.
谁就真的赢下了那一分
So, yeah, I mean, just happy to get through.
所以 就是很高兴能挺过来
In these stressful matches,
这种压力很大的比赛
and that certainly was one at the end,
最后那场确实就是
how much does it help you having
有传奇阿加西
the great Andre Agassi on your bench
坐在你的替补席上
for your confidence?
对你的信心帮助有多大？
It's amazing.
太棒了
I mean, he's giving me more energy
他给我的能量
than everyone else combined, maybe.
可能比其他人加起来还多
But it's great to have him there.
有他在那儿真好
It's great just to have, you know,
真好 场边能有
a voice on the sidelines,
这样一个声音
always encouraging you.
一直在给你鼓劲
And I think just staying mentally calm
而且我觉得保持心态冷静
was very helpful.
帮了很大的忙
Awesome. Well, well done today.
太棒了 今天打得漂亮
You've tied things up.
你把比分扳平了
3-3.
3比3